asknumbers.com 2011-12-28

# Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

Thank you for visiting www.asknumbers.com. We respect your privacy and committed to protect your privacy while online at our site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. The following discloses the information gathering practices for this web site. 

**Advertisers:**

We use third-party advertising companies such as Google to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the internet. Google may be placing and reading cookies on your user browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of generating the most relevant and useful ads for you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Cookies / Tracking Technology :**

A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters sent to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. Our site don’t use cookies but our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, Google Adsense) to improve the quality of their advertisement service. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings if you wish so. 

**Log Files:**

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Links:**

This web site contains some selected links to other web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content and privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personal information. This privacy statement is valid only for the information collected by this web site. 

**Contact Information:**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [webmaster@asknumbers.com](mailto:webmaster@asknumbers.com)

## Terms of Use :

Although all the precautions have been taken in the preparation of these metric conversion, information pages and tables, we assume no responsibility for the errors that have been made. We disclaim all the liability (including negligence) for claims of losses, expenses, damages and costs the user may incur as a result of information on this site. 

Users should independently verify the accuracy, currency, completeness and relevance of the material on this site, or information contained in it. In particular, users should seek independent professional advice before making any investment or business decisions. If you find an error, please report it to us so we will correct it as soon as possible. 

No part of these conversion, information pages and tables shall be reproduced, stored or transmitted by any means, without prior written permission from the publisher.
